<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
 <head>
  <meta name="date" content="2014-01-23T20:28:25Z"></meta>
  <meta name="xmp:CreatorTool" content="Adobe InDesign CS6 (Windows)"></meta>
  <meta name="Keywords" content=""></meta>
  <meta name="subject" content=""></meta>
  <meta name="dc:creator" content="Child &amp; Youth Finance International"></meta>
  <meta name="dcterms:created" content="2014-01-23T11:45:37Z"></meta>
  <meta name="Last-Modified" content="2014-01-23T20:28:25Z"></meta>
  <meta name="dcterms:modified" content="2014-01-23T20:28:25Z"></meta>
  <meta name="Last-Save-Date" content="2014-01-23T20:28:25Z"></meta>
  <meta name="meta:save-date" content="2014-01-23T20:28:25Z"></meta>
  <meta name="dc:title" content="2014 Global Money Week Brochure"></meta>
  <meta name="modified" content="2014-01-23T20:28:25Z"></meta>
  <meta name="Content-Length" content="1577864"></meta>
  <meta name="Content-Type" content="application/pdf"></meta>
  <meta name="creator" content="Child &amp; Youth Finance International"></meta>
  <meta name="meta:author" content="Child &amp; Youth Finance International"></meta>
  <meta name="dc:subject" content=""></meta>
  <meta name="trapped" content="Unknown"></meta>
  <meta name="meta:creation-date" content="2014-01-23T11:45:37Z"></meta>
  <meta name="created" content="Thu Jan 23 12:45:37 CET 2014"></meta>
  <meta name="xmpTPg:NPages" content="2"></meta>
  <meta name="Creation-Date" content="2014-01-23T11:45:37Z"></meta>
  <meta name="resourceName" content="2014-gmw-brochure-english.pdf"></meta>
  <meta name="meta:keyword" content=""></meta>
  <meta name="Author" content="Child &amp; Youth Finance International"></meta>
  <meta name="producer" content="Adobe PDF Library 10.0.1"></meta>
  <title>
   <p>2014 Global Money Week Brochure</p>
  </title>
 </head>
 <body>
  <div class="page">
   <p>10th -17th March 2014</p>
   <p>#GMW2014 #GlobalMoneyWeekGlobal Theme The global theme aims to inspire the celebrations and activities during Global Money Week.</p>
   <p>The theme of 2014 is the Post 2015 Agenda: What do children and youth want for their future?</p>
   <p>Connect with GMW 2014 www.childfinanceinternational.org www.globalmoneyweek.org</p>
   <p>Facebook Like the Global Money Week page and ChildFinance page on Facebook to stay informed and share your celebrations! Twitter</p>
   <p>Follow @GlobalMoneyWeek and @ChildFinance on Twitter to get constant updates about the celebrations.</p>
   <p>Use the hashtags #GMW2014 or #GlobalMoneyWeek to share about your events.</p>
   <p>Get in Touch Liina Liblik Communications Coordinator Child &amp; Youth Finance International Liina@childfinance.org +31 20 5203900</p>
   <p>Robin Willing Director of Communications &amp; Operations Child &amp; Youth Finance International Robin@childfinance.org +31 20 5203900</p>
   <p>Child and Youth Finance International PO Box 16524 1001 RA Amsterdam Netherlands + 31(0)20 5203900</p>
   <p>About Global Money Week Global Money Week is a worldwide celebration to empower the next generation to be confident, responsible and skilled economic citizens. It is about joining together – children, youth, parents, organizations and entire communities - to start action to reshape finance, and give young people the tools to shape their own future.</p>
   <p>Global Money Week 2013 • 1 million children &amp; youth and their families • 185 partner organizations • 80 countries</p>
   <p>Get Involved! Ready to celebrate? Contact your national committee to involve your company, organization, school or youth group in Global Money Week 2014. If you do not already have direct contact with your national committee, please contact the CYFI Secretariat and they will connect you.</p>
   <div class="annotation">
    <a href="https://twitter.com/ChildFinance"></a>
   </div>
   <div class="annotation">
    <a href="http://www.childfinanceinternational.org/"></a>
   </div>
   <div class="annotation">
    <a href="http://www.globalmoneyweek.org"></a>
   </div>
   <div class="annotation">
    <a href="http://www.facebook.com/GlobalMoneyWeek"></a>
   </div>
   <div class="annotation">
    <a href="http://twitter.com/GlobalMoneyWeek"></a>
   </div>
   <div class="annotation">
    <a href="http://twitter.com/childfinance"></a>
   </div>
  </div>
  <div class="page">
   <p>Youth take action to Reshape Finance! The aim of Global Money Week is to encourage youth to share their ideas – but also to elevate these ideas and motivate action. The celebrations are concentrated in one week, but the impact of the ideas and lessons during this week will have long-lasting impact and bring about action. Youth need to be a part of the changes for their future- the decision makers of tomorrow need to be a part of the policy discussions of today!</p>
   <p>Share and Promote Global Money Week is a great opportunity to share the initiatives that have been made in your country or by your organization during the year with the rest of the world. By sharing your progress you help to promote and inspire Economic Citizenship Education and the empowerment of youth worldwide.</p>
   <p>10th -17th March 2014 Celebrating Global Money Week!</p>
   <p>Global Activities - Connecting the World Global Activities are aimed at crossing borders and share the celebrations of countires with everyone celebrating Global Money Week around the globe. Via online live streaming, webinars and video chats countires are connected all over the world.</p>
   <p>• Global Web Chat Café – Young people from all over the world connect with their peers to share stories, learn from each other and inspire one another to take action.</p>
   <p>• VIP Talks – Live streamed talks by inspiring persons. Youngsters connect with the persons that inspire them and ask the questions they care about.</p>
   <p>• Youth and PolicyMakers Global Dialogue – Online chats with youth and policymakers such as governors of central banks and ministers of finance and education.</p>
   <p>• Youth Talks – Youth talking to youth or inspiring academics talk to youth on entrepreneurship, financial education and financial inclusion. These talks will take place at schools and universities.</p>
   <p>About Child &amp; Youth Finance International Child and Youth Finance International (CYFI) serves as a platform to align and support GMW activities all over the world in coordination with national financial inclusion platform committees in every country.</p>
   <p>CYFI leads the world’s largest Movement dedicated to enhancing the financial capabilities of children and youth. Launched in April 2012, the Movement has already spread to over 100 countries and has reached more than 18 million children. Its partners and supporters include financial authorities and some of the world’s leading financial institutions, international NGOs, multilateral and bilateral institutions, foundations, renowned academics, and children and youth.</p>
   <p>National Activities Only your imagination sets the limits for the activities and events that can be organized to celebrate Global Money Week at a national level. Below are some of the many inspiring events that have been organized during previous celebrations.</p>
   <p>• ART &amp; CREATIVITY • Theatre • Storytelling • Art Exhibitions • Cartoons • Writing Songs • Make your own • VISITS • Visits to banks • Visits to the stock exchange and ringing the opening bell to signal the beginning of trade • Visits to money museums • Visit to businesses • Learning from the market • GAMES &amp; COMPETITIONS • Poster-making contests • Financial Football • Financial education games • MEDIA • Radio talk shows • Social Media • TV shows • Video Making • EDUCATION &amp; PROJECTS • Young entrepreneur • Projects Workshops and financial education lessons • Special book banks • Youth budget to parliament • Debates • Research and Petition</p>
  </div>
 </body>
</html>